LOUIS MOSES A. RAIT

Email: louismoses.rait@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/lm-rait/

Mobile/WhatsApp No. : +639605049152

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To apply and enhance my skills, knowledge, experience and interest in the field of website development, and be further adapted in a related organization as an effective, motivated and efficient individual in the achievement of its goal, vision and mission.

SKILLS

- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Premier Pro
 Adobe Photoshop CC
 AutoCAD 2D
 CSS3
 JavaScript
 WordPress
- AutoCAD 2D
- Bootstrap

- HTML
- CSS3

- Basic SEO Optimization
- DIVI Theme Builder
- Elementor
- Network System Troubleshooting

EXPERIENCE

Accenture

Application Developer

Salesforce Bootcamp Training

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

ZTE Philippines Inc.

Product Technical Engineer

- Optical Line Terminal
 - Compatibility test with Optical Network Unit(ONU)
 - OLT/ONU Setup and Configuration
 - Technical Site Survey Report
- CPE's Field/Actual Test
 - Indoor and Outdoor Performance
 - Data logs
 - Comparison Test with type approved device
- Firmware Update
 - Flash new/updated firmware
 - Check Graphical User Interface (GUI)
 - Settings functionality
- Assistance on Customer-side Test
 - ISDP Security Test
 - SICE
 - AEPM
 - CFS
 - DCM UAT
- Provide Customer Support
 - Basic System Troubleshooting
 - Network Log Capture
- NTC Type Approval Application
 - Form Application/Documentation and follow up.

Jan 2021 - Aug 2022

National Strategic Group Inc.

WordPress Frontend Web Developer

- Jan 2019 Aug 2022
- Build website using WordPress and DIVI Theme Builder
- Convert PSD Design to website landing page
- Write semantic HTML and CSS
- Customize themes to meet clients' requirements
- Maintain and update website
- Check website responsiveness on different devices

VA Staffer

♣ WordPress Frontend Web Developer / Virtual Assistant

Jun 2016 - Dec 2018

- Design websites and Social Media Graphics
- Convert PSD Design to WordPress website
- Check website responsiveness on different devices
- Maintain and updates websites
- Edit audio for podcast
- Video Editing
- Kinetic Typologies

Total Gaming Technologies Inc.

April - October 2015

- Network Admin Assistant
 - Configure modems
 - Sim card IP tagging
 - Process new outlet installations and transfer
 - On-phone technical support
 - Outlet surveying and troubleshooting.

EDUCATION

AMA Computer College

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

2014

ADDITIONAL

TEAM MINISTRIES LUCENA

Sound Technician

Jan 2006 – Present

- Digital and Analog Audio System Operation
- Manage and Maintain Audio Equipment
- Audio Signal Flow and Troubleshooting
- Speaker Control
- Feedback Control